Ah, done with another
grueling day of school.
Now all I want to do is go home and relax.
Huh? Huh?
Uh, Koichi, it's… you.
Hey there, Hazamada.
Oh, yeah, hi, what's new?
I'm sorry about all the trouble
I gave you the other day.
So, uh, have you completely
recovered from your injuries?
Sort of, I guess.
The talk sent me home two days ago.
Where's that bastard?
I mean, where's Josuke?
He probably already went home.
You won't believe it, but he
found an invisible baby yesterday.
And now they're bending over
backwards to find its mother.
So the baby is a stand user?
Looks that way.
Apparently, the baby has formed
a bond with Josuke's dad, Mr.
Joestar.
In fact, if Mr.
Joestar isn't nearby at all times, she
turns everything around her invisible.
Hmm...
Does this mean this Mr.
Joestar is gonna stick
around Morioh for a while?
Probably.
I see.
Hey, Koichi, do you happen
to like manga? Manga?
Yeah, guess I like him
as much as the next guy.
Have you ever heard of Rohan Kishibe?
He draws Pink Dark Boy!
What kind of question is that?
I'm one of the biggest Pink
Dark Boy fans in Japan!
No way!
You really like it?
You're talking about the suspense
horror series, aren't you?
I never get it mixed
up with anything else!
It can get pretty gross sometimes,
but it's worth it for the horror
aesthetic and complex characters.
I completely agree!
By the way, here's a little secret.
Rohan Kishibe actually
lives right here in Morioh.
What?
Did I hear you right?
He lives here in Morioh?
It's almost too good to
be true, are you sure?
I know, I couldn't believe it either!
I heard some realtors talking about
it while I was at the comic store.
It's mind-boggling news,
but it's absolutely true!
Yeah!
I just had a great idea!
Let's get some autographs!
You know it!
Just lead the way!
We really get each
other, huh? You think so?
Hey, look up there!
I think that might be his studio.
The light's on!
Yeah, you're right.
Hey, I wonder if Rohan has any family.
From what I hear, he lives alone.
He made his debut four years
ago, back when he was 16.
Say what?
He's only 20 years old?
That means he was about
my age when he went pro.
Snooping around out here
won't do us any good, Koichi.
You're gonna have to ring the doorbell.
Huh?
But why do I have to do it?
Isn't it obvious?
I have seniority over you.
And to be honest, this kind
of stuff makes me nervous.
Oh, that's not fair at all.
I recognize him!
It's Rohan Kishibe!
He looks just like his picture
on the cover of that special
New Year's edition!
I mean, Mr. Rohan!
And who, pray tell, are you?
Why are you here?
Some kind of prank? No!
We'd never do that!
Honest!
We're students from
Burugahoka High School!
Yeah, we're fans of yours,
Sensei! Fans? Of me? Really?
My address must have gotten leaked.
That's not it at all.
I just happened to hear it in passing.
I hope it's not too much trouble, Mr.
Rohan, but could we have
a couple of autographs?
It'd really make our day.
So you're fans, eh?
Tremendous.
We might just be on the same wavelength.
Nothing, don't mind me.
Please come in.
It'd be a pleasure to sign autographs
for two of my biggest fans.
You see?
Aren't you glad we came?
I know.
How would you like a little
studio tour while you're here?
You'd really let us see
where the magic happens?
I've already finished today's work,
but if you're still interested then...
We are!
Pardon the intrusion!
Here it is.
Oh, amazing!
Whoa, those are four color originals!
Oh, stunning!
It's even more powerful in person!
This is the most magical day ever!
I'm so glad we're here!
So I have to know, sensei, how long
have you been working at a Morioh?
I've been living here
for about three months.
My family lives in S-City,
but when I was a child, we
actually called Mariah our home.
Tokyo has its perks, but it's too chaotic.
It has none of Morio's serenity and
isn't at all conducive to creativity.
And besides,
today's fax machines and photocopiers
are more advanced than they've ever been.
I can send a complete
manuscript in four hours.
No point living in the city now, unless
you care about status and all that drivel.
So, uh, what about your
assistants and staff?
How do they factor in? They don't.
I work alone. What?
There's just no way!
You get 19 pages of complex
drawings done in a week!
Four days, actually. What?
Five if they're in color.
On off days, I amuse myself
with travel and such.
I'm not much of a people person, which
is why I chose to be a manga artist.
An assistant would only be
an unnecessary hindrance.
Wow, that's so amazing!
You're a total genius!
Please, excuse me.
It's a spider!
Suburbia never ceases to amaze
with its bugs and spiders.
Uh, Mr. Rohan? I see.
Hello, Arrhenius ventricosis.
It inhabits homes and
rural areas across Japan.
It's an orb-weaving spider.
And a number of them
weave webs day and night.
By the way, you two,
do you know what it takes to create
captivating stories for manga?
Reality, reality is the driving force
that makes a drawing come totally alive.
Its entertainment on the
highest possible level.
People assume manga is born
of imagination and fantasy,
but they couldn't be more wrong.
A great manga is one that
captures things experienced,
seen and felt by flesh and blood beings.
Take this exquisite spider for example,
something a typical city
dweller would kill in disgust.
The way the legs connect to the body
and the positions of its many eyes.
Even subtle differences
between the male and female.
A manga artist must understand each
of these elements to draw a spider.
It's said a spider's silk
solidifies when exposed to air.
But have you ever given any
thought to its spinnerets?
And then there's the intricate
arrangement of its internal organs.
How does a spider squirm,
especially when it's been sliced
open and awaiting certain death?
To depict reality in detail,
one must know such things.
That's barbaric! Silence!
How dare an amateur like you
give Rohan Kishibe his opinion!
No, I wasn't voicing my
opinion at all! I'm sorry.
Now it's time for a taste.
Holy shit, the stereotype is true!
Manga artists really are total weirdos!
An excellent expression of agony.
Your vomiting reflex is so raw,
I simply must sketch it. Really?
And now you're just pretending.
Let's forget about the sketch.
It won't be of any use.
Oh, I'm sorry.
You wanted autographs.
I'll see if I can find
a pen in the kitchen.
I'll bring some tea out as well.
You don't have to do that!
Rohan is great! What a process!
Now I know what makes
Pink Dark Boy so amazing!
His need to know every single
detail is on another level!
Um, Azamara?
I know we just got here and all, but...
Well, uh, don't you think it's
about time for us to get going?
Say what?
You want to go home now?
But why?
Aren't you having fun?
I can't really say why I'm
so nervous all of a sudden.
I just have a bad feeling about this.
My gut has been known to
be wrong on rare occasions,
but right now it's telling me that there's
something really dangerous about Rohan.
Dangerous?
What do you mean by that?
You think he's a stan user?
No, no, it's nothing like that.
It's just a weird feeling.
Rohan is what those hippie artist
types would call avant-garde,
but that doesn't mean
you should immediately
jump to conclusions about
him being a stan user.
I already told you, I
don't think he is one.
I just have a bad feeling, is all.
Okay, okay. Let's say Mr.
Rohan actually is a stand user.
That'd be amazing for us, don't you think?
How awesome would it be to have something
in common with a famous manga artist?
But I feel you. So let's leave.
If something about him's giving
you the willies, then let's go.
Come on.
We can always come back.
But one catch!
This thing caught my eye, so
I have to check it out first.
A thing? Where?
What are you talking about?
Jeez, Koichi, you're so tense.
There, it's on top of the
desk next to the phone.
Look carefully.
Could that be what I think it is?
You better believe it is!
He said he just finished
working on it, remember?
I've had my eye on it since we came
in here, and it's the real deal!
I never dreamed this would happen.
A freshly drawn manuscript
for Pink Dark Boy.
Hang on, does this mean
no one else has seen it?
We'll go home right after
I get a glimpse of this.
We have to get Rohan's permission first.
You really don't know anything
about manga artists, do you, Koichi?
All of these pre-printed manuscripts are
highly confidential in
every sense of the word.
There's no way he'd let a couple
of outsiders like us look at
a manuscript before the editors
even had a chance to give notes.
It's common sense.
We'll take a peek, then put it right back.
This is a horrible idea. Lighten up.
We're not hurting anyone by reading it.
What is this feeling?
I know it's a thrilling manga, but
seeing an abusive person like this?
is giving me major
goosebumps all over my body!
It's so good!
Hurry up and turn the page, Hazamada!
I have to know what comes next!
I'm getting emotional!
What do you know?
It appears my manuscript's
compatible with you two after all.
How auspicious.
I had a hunch you might read it.
Good work, boys.
The two of you are compatible
first-time readers of my new manuscript.
As I'm not I?
What's the matter?
You will now experience my
glorious ability, Heaven's Door.
It's a gateway to your very souls.
What do you mean?
What is going on?
Why does my hand feel weird?
What the?
Koichi, what the hell is happening to you?
Many things are recorded in the human
body over the course of one's life.
Every single thing from
the moment you were born.
To peruse your records I shall
transform you both into books.
Magnificent books that
chronicle your life's stories.
Not me!
Somebody else!
I believe you read my manga as well.
It's happening to me!
My ability won't physically harm
you, so there's no need to worry.
What the hell do you
even want from us anyway?
In manga, the creator's sense of
reality is critical, remember?
We went over that.
So now, I will read all about your
lives and experiences thus far,
and these pages will fill my
consciousness with realistic ideas.
More effective than an interview,
you will tell me everything you've
lived through with 100 % accuracy,
as if I had been there
to experience it myself!
Koichi Hirose, born March
28, 1984, at 6.27 a .m.
You were delivered at Red
Cross Hospital in S-City.
A preemie of 2,325 grams, you
spent a week in an incubator.
A family of four and an
older sister named Ayana.
Yes, I see.
In grade school and middle school,
you led a relatively ordinary life.
You also happened to be a
remarkably genuine soul.
An admirable quality.
What is this?
So then you're hiding a secret
ability, are you? Reverb, huh?
And it seems that there
are other individuals
in the world with these
fantastical abilities.
You have powers, too?
Stand users, huh? Astounding!
Everything in here dated after
April 1999 is just extraordinary!
An explosion of wondrous experiences!
Josuke Higashikata, Jotaro Kujo,
Yukako Yamagishi, Okuyasu
Nijimura, Tamami Kobayashi!
Oh, it's unbelievable!
Incredible and utterly captivating.
In these pages, Koichi Hirose,
I've just uncovered the
mother load of manga material.
Shining Diamond, Star Platinum, The
Hand, Love Deluxe, et Star, et Star.
What are you talking about?
What the heck are you
planning to do to us now?
You mean it isn't obvious yet?
I'm going to use your memories
to write my manga. River!
I'm only going to ask you nicely once
to stop attacking us with your stand,
if you persist.
Hmm, what will you do?
Strike me with reverb act two
sound attack? Just try it.
Don't test me.
If you don't release me from your
stand right now, I won't hold back.
This is your last chance.
Yes, I know.
There's actually a section devoted
to that written on page 11.
You've always been far more
timid than most others,
and many tend to blatantly disrespect you.
But when push comes to shove, you find
the courage to conquer your fears.
Remarkable.
I like you already.
And as for my readers, they'll feel
the same once they get to know you.
I'm not bluffing, you hear me?
I'll attack if I have to.
You really don't know
when to shut up, do you?
Try it if you dare!
Reverb, act two, go!
I don't get it!
How'd my attack miss?
You honestly missed at that range?
I thought you let it go wide on purpose!
I hate to break it to
you, but your aim is shit!
I won't miss this time!
Where are you attacking?
That wasn't even close!
Unfortunately for you, Koichi,
I took the liberty of placing
a little safety lock on Reverb.
You can attack me to your heart's content,
but you're no longer able to land a blow.
Safety lock?
Take a look.
It's in the margin on page 11.
I added that new rule as a
little bit of a safety measure,
just in case you used your stand.
Do you see?
This is the awesome
power of Heaven's Door.
Through it,
I can use words and
pictures to read people's
experiences or create brand new memories.
It doesn't matter what sort of
tricks you have up your sleeve.
You'll never be able to do me
harm as long as I have this power.
Shit!
What do I do now?
Chin up, Koichi.
That's all the tampering I intend to do.
If I meddled with your pages any further,
your precious life would
lose all authenticity?
and you'd no longer be of
any benefit to my work.
All right.
Now let's have a look
at your pages, Hazamada.
You're a genius in every
sense of the word, sir!
I respect you so much!
I suppose we'll see about that. Now then,
you sometimes find a sense of comfort
in picking on creatures weaker than you?
like helpless kittens and small birds.
You want to have your way with
Junko, a junior from Class E,
but are too cowardly to act on it.
Your testicles often grow sweaty, and
when you adjust them during class,
nothing thrills you more than the thought?
that someone might see you.
You're a disgusting troll.
Including someone like you in my
manga would drive readers away.
You're useless.
What am I gonna do now?
I'm hopeless. Why?
Why are you doing this?
You don't need any of my
experiences to create stories.
You're a spectacular manga
artist all on your own.
Every reader in the world knows that.
Also, you're only 20 years old
and live in this amazing house.
Think of how blessed you are
compared with most people your age.
So why do you need my memories
when you're already grey?
How stupid can you be?
Do you think that I, Rohan Kishibe, draw
manga to gather money and admiration?
I draw manga so that people
around the world will read it.
My only objective is for
people to read my work.
I know it's a single simple reason.
Even so, it's all I care about.
People want honesty
when they read my work,
so I search for inspirational
realism every day.
And truth be told, I absolutely love
the feeling of finishing a manuscript.
Everyone feels good after finishing
a project they've worked hard on,
but that gratification is
fleeting and immaterial.
After the initial rush
of euphoria is gone,
I begin to think no one will
read the manga I slaved over?
and my deep-seated
insecurities begin to flare up.
What if all my readers
are gone by next week?
What if I don't know what
to draw for the next issue?
What if I lose the ability to draw?
What if my motivation disappears?
These are the recurring thoughts
that have tormented me over and over?
since I was a 16-year-old novice.
Until three months ago when a mysterious
stranger shot me to the core with an arrow?
and I gained the ability of Heaven's Door.
That was Keicho Nichimura.
Yes, I saw his name written on your pages.
You two have no idea what it's like
to find the perfect inspiration?
for your ultimate masterpiece.
But I found it at last.
There's nothing better.
Koichi, I'm taking your reality and
using it as a muse for my new stories!
See, Koichi, I told you Mr.
Rohan was a super nice guy.
Aren't you glad we decided
to pay him a visit?
Definitely, I had a ton of fun.
Not only did he give us
these great autographs,
He was even kind enough to
serve us tea and cookies.
Mm-hmm.
I want to go back as soon as we can.
Me too.
Today kicked ass!
Well, I'm headed this way.
See you later.
I'm still surprised he
was such a great guy.
You'll never speak of what
happened, right, Koichi?
What the?
How the heck did I lose 20 kilograms?
That's so weird.
I look exactly the same.
Yep, it reads 5 kilograms,
so the scale's not broken.
This doesn't make any sense!
Wait, this must be the work
of an enemy stand user!
There's no other way I could
possibly lose 20 kilograms this fast!
But who's the user?
I have to talk to Josuke about the -
Huh?
Hey, Ko, what are you
doing over there? Huh?
Me?
Uh, well, I...
Huh, what was it?
What the hell are you
talking about, you weirdo?
Hey, what's wrong?
Oh, it's just my brother.
For some reason, he's wandering
around the house in his goofy boxers.
What was it?
I could have sworn I was thinking about
something really important a second ago.
Well, if I managed to forget so easily,
it couldn't have been that important.
Oh, man.
Why do my shoes and bag feel
heavier than usual today? Hold on.
This house!
How strange.
Somehow, I ended up walking all
the way back to Rohan's house.
The door's open.
I'd like to drop in and thank him for
being such a great host yesterday.
But I'll be late for school.
I probably shouldn't.
Being an artist, he's
probably still asleep.
It'd be rude to just barge in.
I really shouldn't.
You saw that, right, Okuyasu?
Yeah...
Spying feels wrong,
but it's out of character for Koichi
to act so weird and ditch school.
What the hell is he doing?
Well, I want to know who
in the world lives here.
I mean, there's no way he's
meeting up with some chick, right?
Rohan,
he's working with such a chilling
expression and for some reason I
can't shake the feeling that being
in this house is actually terrifying?
Why you finally made it?
It's good to see you!
Right on time for our session.
We'll
be
right back.